Here we go, Apkami, this time with Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory and
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the UPRONT Group.
We will show you the process of recording, rehearsing, and other aspects of our production.
We'll start off with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs as they go through the process of recording, rehearsing, and other aspects of their work.
Let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Tanimoto, would like to talk about Akira Shinuma's graduation lecture that was held at the Nippon Budokan the other day,
This was the graduation performance of Shinnuma Kisora, a member who has been with us since the formation of the group and with whom we were very close.
I felt that I really had to do my best in this performance.
I was able to finish the performance with a smile on my face.
But when it came to the performance, memories of the past came flooding back to me.
I really wondered what was going to happen until the end.
I tried my best to hold back the tears, but I couldn't finish the show with a smile on my face.
I couldn't finish the show with a smile on my face.
But I could not finish with a smile on my face.
I did my best to express what I wanted to say to Kisora-chan, so I think it was a good thing that I was able to do so.
Five members Numaki-chan was graduating, so I became the next leader of the group.
I introduced myself as Tsubaki Factory, but before that, the leader said "I'm Tsubaki Factory".
But before that, the leader says "I'm from Tsubaki Factory" and the leader says "I'm from Tsubaki Factory".
After Kisora-chan graduated, I started saying "Se-no".
I felt that I became the leader of Tsubaki Factory.
Yes, I, Imigeta, am.
After Ms. Ishida's graduation, I recently started to learn dance and ballet.
I'd like to talk about that.
Yes, Ms. Ishida is graduating at the end of December.
Ishida will graduate at the end of December.
the end of December.
I have been learning dance and ballet
I've been learning dance and ballet since I was little.
but since I came to Tokyo, I haven't been able to learn them at all.
I knew that Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
Morning Musume is also about dancing.
I knew that I mustn't ruin the image of Morning Musume.
I was a guest at the presentation of the trainees, wasn't I?
That was the first time I saw the trainees' performance from the sleeve at a very close distance.
I saw the trainees' performance from the sleeve for the first time.
It was amazing.
I saw them dance, and it was amazing.
I realized that I couldn't lose to them, so I'd like to keep up the good work.
I'm going to keep up the good work!
I'm going to keep up the good work.
When I see her dance formations like this...
I always think you're so cool.
I'm looking forward to seeing more of your dance moves in the future!
Now, let's start from here.
The making of Angelem's Rumors of Narcissi music video shoot
It was released on June 12!
From Angulum's latest single
Here's a look at the making of the music video for "Rumor of Narcissi"!
Today, we're going to shoot a lip for Narcsy's music video.
I'm going to shoot a solo lip.
I always wear my hair on this ear, so this angle is good.
But today, I'm wearing my hair this way, and I'm trying to imagine taking the shot from this angle, which I'm not used to.
I'll do my best, and I'll see you soon.
I'm not listening to Mr. Boy's opinion.
It's brighter than it looks.
Pick one.
It's all in good taste.
I see the pitch flicker in your eyes as we pass each other.
Then maybe you'll come back... there, there, there...
Magic card music
Drunken Dancing
Colorful hair, tears
Even if you're not very good at it, you're still cute
Don't be so full of confidence
It's a cool or blue
Muragaru reply
Gotha Gotha Gotha Chal Rufai
Hey! Rumor has it, Doshi
Who cares what it's called I love
My self
Gathering Chelasi
The happiest in the universe
I'm sorry
There's no end to the comparisons
Hands don't compare
Well, then, admit it.
I want to love each and every one of you individually and specifically
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
There was a solo lip ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah. I will properly become the main character and raise my heart.
Yes, I'm still a little embarrassed.
It's a lot. One more step, one more step, one more step, one more part, one more nuance than the last...
Choose.
Colors
When everything is different, no, no, no.
So you want to dance?
Trablers Magical Music.
I'm not prepared
Colorful hair, dazzle me.
Even if it's a story, the technique is the skill
You can't be too full of confidence
It's a cool world
Drill, village girl
Bibler Gontan Gontan
Skulls Sky
Rumor of the Nanoshi
Who the hell is that?
Aitaita
I'm very, very serious about it.
I think it will be a good work.
I have a feeling that it will be a good work.
It's wonderful!
I didn't have time to enjoy it. I took it too seriously.
I was so serious about it that at first my face was like this.
But gradually, I felt like I was loosening up.
Thank you very much.
Please pay attention to the expression on his face!
Which one of us can't you see?
Okay, please roll the camera.
Music, please.
Background music, please.
Oh, my God! That was good!
Yes, we've finished shooting the music video for NARCY!
We shot in this building today, in a lot of different locations.
We shot some dance shots when we could see the ocean.
We also used the stairs.
We also went outside to the pool.
Lying on the mirror
Each shot was taken in the members' threads, and they left a great impression on me,
The color of lying outside in the mirror was really beautiful,
I was thrilled by the new experience of really lying on the mirror,
I'm also very curious to see how it is used in the film.
We are looking forward to seeing how the film will turn out, and I think it was a very enjoyable shoot that resulted in a really wonderful film.
I hope you will watch it a lot.
I've always had an image of Angstrom as being really strong, but this music video has a more mature, relaxed, and relaxed image.
I wonder what it is like to see a mature, relaxed, adult-like Angsturm.
I was really impressed by Angstrom's ability to express themselves in various ways.
I also really feel like I'm in a café.
It's really something like that vivitar blow.
It's like ahhhhh...
I felt like I was listening to both songs together, and I felt like I was listening to Ms. Sasaki.
I wish I could sleep in a mirror too.
It's nice, isn't it?
It looks like you're having fun at the beach.
It was so nice and refreshing.
That's all for the making of the music video for "Rumor of Narcissi" by Angelem.
That's all for the making of the music video shoot. Please check out the rest of the video.
Next, here we go!
Apkami Photo Gallery
This is the second half of the photo shoot.
This time we are talking about dance.
What kind of contents are we talking about?
Let's take a look.
This is Momo Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory.
In this corner, we discuss a certain subject with Hello Project members,
Let's deepen our understanding of each other and get to know each other better.
Let's discuss and deepen our understanding of each other and get to know each other better!
And finally, let's write on this board some of the memorable words from the talk and take a picture of them.
Let's write them on this board and take a picture of them.
Rather than everyone doing the same play
It's more like you are playing your own role.
Each one of us is a different person.
Each one of us expresses one world as a different person.
So I think that if we don't make sure that all the parts are in the same place, we won't be able to make the most of it.
So I'd like to go one more step.
Let's talk about how to remember.
You learn choreography and staging quickly, don't you?
I'm sure I'm fast. I've been told by the members that I'm fast,
But in my mind, it's not like that at all.
But I am of the school of thought that I should do it 100 times or so to remember.
There are those who learn by watching, right? I definitely have to use my body.
I can't do it unless I dance and memorize with all my might.
I envy those who can learn by watching, but I have to really dance to get it into my body.
Sometimes I think it's a little bit difficult.
But the more I do it, the more confident I become.
I think it's my way of learning.
Well, I'm fast.
I'm fast.
I'm fast. I'm fast, but I'm not fast.
Not really.
You seem to be gaining confidence at the Halo Pro Dance Academy.
Yes, like every time.
You spend a day learning another genre, and then you have to learn the Japanese version for the showcase.
I have to learn it in less than a few hours.
So, you have to be a genius and fast.
There are several members of GAS Gakuen.
I'm slow, too.
You say that a lot.
That's right.
The two of us.
You say that a lot.
I say it like I can't remember.
Maybe that's because you're the fastest person back in the group.
You're right. You're right.
It's a problem, isn't it?
How do you learn it, Mio? Do you put it in your body?
When I watch the videos, I slow them down and memorize them one by one.
I guess it's because I used to be a classical ballet dancer.
It's not so much that I memorize each one.
It's more like the flow of movement from one movement to the next.
I remember the flow of movement from one movement to the next.
I think that when I remember one movement, I remember the next one.
Recently, I've been analyzing this myself.
But when I actually memorize them in the choreography
It's slow.
Is there a girl in the salon who is fast?
Saya Eguchi and Utano Satoyoshi?
That's right.
Those two are by far the fastest.
What is it? I can't help it, I'm in a mountain lodge.
I gave up on the first day and said, "I'll learn if I sleep.
I'm sure you don't think I'm doing too much because I'm pushing myself too hard...
I'm trying, but... but isn't it a little bit different to learn free dance and staging?
I'm sure it's true that I write down the staging one by one, but what about you, Akiyama-san? How about you, Akiyama-san?
I'm a little bit strange, but I'm like, "This is the choreography for this part, that's why it was number 3.
What?
When I came to this part, I was like, "Gosh! I'm like, "Oh!
They made the stage with rehearsal tapes and so on,
Standing there, I was like, "I'm going to go and see my own group.
I would go to the stage myself, and then I would say something like, "I remember you said this earlier..." and so on.
I would stand there and say, "I remember you said this when you were dancing here.
It's a little bit sensory, but it's like, "Hey, I got the choreography code, so let's learn it.
I remember the choreography code, so I remember it like that.
There are so many versions of each song, so many different kinds of magic, so many different kinds of magic, so many different kinds of magic, so many different kinds of magic, so many different kinds of magic, so many different kinds of magic, so many different kinds of magic.
You guys are so good at it, but you don't know what the number is for one song, what the core is, and there's so many rows and columns.
I don't know what the core is, and there's a lot of lines.
I'm just thinking about it and I'm like, "Wow, this is amazing! I think I'm doing a great job.
I think it would be great if you and Miyu could learn it faster, wouldn't it?
I'll do my best! I'll do my best!
Okay, let's move on to the next one, shall we?
Wow, I'm on a dime! What shall we do?
Uh, tuning! Adjustment! Wow, I'm torn. What shall we do?
Adjustment.
Balance of dance performance in a group
I'm talking about the balance of dance performance in a group,
You have a percentage that allows you to express yourself to the maximum,
But what do you do when you dance in a group?
I have always placed great importance on dancing accurately.
It is the most important thing for me.
So I don't think I will ever deviate from the average.
Of course, I have never thought that I am 100% correct.
That's why I sometimes see the differences of others.
That's what makes it so difficult.
I think that's one of the problems of working in a group.
It's not just about being right.
It's not just about being right, it's about pretending there's a right answer.
It depends on who is doing it with whom.
There are different values depending on who is doing it with whom.
I'm trying to find out at the beginning.
How much of yourself do you put out there?
How much of yourself do you put out, or do you stick to the original pretense?
That's something I have a lot of trouble with.
Also, when I think about the relationship between the choreography and the sound
I'm the type of person who can't move on to the next movement until the sound comes.
So, if there is one movement
So, if there is one movement, if I have to learn it one by one like this
I can dance independently from the music.
But in my case, there is a mass of sound
and I put each movement on it.
I have to wait until I get there.
or something like that.
I have to wait for
I have to make sure that I use up all of the moves
I have to use up all of it
I have that kind of awareness.
On the other hand, there are times
It's a problem.
It's a problem... but everyone has their own personality... but that's great too.
I think it's great to dance together, and I think it's great that some people are a little more free than others.
That's what makes it so difficult.
It's difficult, isn't it?
But I think it's difficult to tolerate it.
Yes, that's true.
I also think that the balance of dance in this group is important.
I don't think the members from the debut period are very good at it.
The songs are the same, but maybe not so much. It's a bit sad. I don't dance much.
I like dancing, so there was a part of me that was trying too hard in the past.
That's why some people said that my dancing was a little too flamboyant, that I was showing off a little too much.
But I thought that opinion was true.
I thought that I was right, but then I started to think about how much my dancing should be divergent from the music, and to be honest, I am still troubled by it.
I've thought about it a lot, and even now, I'm still troubled by it, but in a really good way, Tsubaki has a lot of different genres, and there's cute, cool, and cutting.
There are cute, cool, sad, dance, rock, and so on.
I think it can be dyed in any color, so I've been thinking recently that it would be nice if I could be various kinds of myself in response to the songs.
That's why I didn't move too much in this song.
In the song "My Darling Do You Love Me," I don't dance too much.
Like grabbing the sleeve of the person you like
Like calling out to the person you love...
I just nod my head a little bit.
But when I dance to a song, I give it everything I've got.
I'm really enjoying changing it up depending on the song.
I think that balance is very important.
I've also felt it through the opinions of the fans.
But it's precisely because we're a group that I'm able to think this way.
I've come to be able to think this way.
I'm learning every day.
I don't think I was good at what I'm pointing out now.
I was too focused on what I wanted to do.
I didn't think about everyone else.
I'm thinking about it a lot.
I hope to brush up more and more in the value of the relationship with everyone from now on.
Now, I've talked about a lot of things so far, but
I would like to write down some of the words that left an impression on me during this talk.
I, Mao Akiyama
Jang-jang (rock, paper, scissors)
The role of each one of us that I was talking about in the role.
I mean
Miyo Hirai just said
There are a lot of acting parts in the Beyoncé song.
It's because each one of us has a role to play.
It's precisely because each person has a role that everyone can play together, and it's precisely because each person has a role that everyone can play together that everyone can play together.
I felt that this difference is unique to the Beyoncés when we talked about it.
I felt it was something that was unique to the Beyoncés.
I felt that this story would not have been possible without the Beyoncés.
When all the members sing together, there is a showcase for the group and a showcase for each of us.
I felt like I could hear your thoughts deeply today, and I was really happy to hear them.
I really love BEYOND's songs because they are fun to watch.
I'd like to see more of BEYOND's music, and I'd like to see more of each of them, and to see each song as a whole.
I'd like to see more of each of them, and I'd like to see each of them on their own in the future.
Well, I'm Ja-jan.
I would like to talk about the theme of the talk, "Adjustment", which was about how it would be great if I could become various kinds of people.
I think Mr. Akiyama was talking about how he wished he could be various kinds of people.
This is related to this, too, but...
I have various characters or personalities depending on the song, but I still want to be Hirai Miyo.
But I am still Hirai Miyo, and I am still Hirai Miyo.
In other groups, I feel like I'm a girl in love or a woman in love.
I think there are a lot of things like women and so on, but
But I was still myself.
I was still myself, so I was not surprised to find out that it is okay to be fully open in my approach to performance,
I chose this word because I thought it was a great new discovery.
I think it was a great new discovery for me, so I chose this word.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
let's go!
I got the picture.
I was so surprised.
If Akiyama-san and Hirai-san are so slow in learning how to dance...
what about me? It was like...
I thought I was pretty fast.
But now I'm not so sure.
For a long time, many people watched the concert videos and memorized the choreography on their own.
I learned the choreography on my own.
I used to do it in front of my mother.
I think I'm a pretty quick learner of choreography
But I'm the kind of person who forgets them easily.
That's why at the last Hina Fest
I'm the kind of person who easily forgets the choreography. at the last Hina Fest.
I wanted to destroy them.
Each piece is difficult and the songs are quite long, so it took me three days to get to the first one, "Ano Rukunro Kamoong".
It took me three days to get to the first one, "Rukunro Kamoom".
It took me about a week to learn it.
I'm going to do my best just like you, Mr. Akiyama.
I'll do my best!
It's really hard to remember the choreography.
In my case, I'm the slowest in the group in learning the choreography.
I haven't been dancing since I was a child, so when I joined Hello Project, I finally learned how to dance one by one.
I've been learning dances one by one since I joined Hello Project.
When I was learning the choreography, I always wondered
What is this choreography?
First of all, I start by asking myself, "How does this dance work?
That's really difficult for me.
So I always rely on Mao Akiyama because she is a good dancer.
So I'm really grateful to Mao Akiyama because she teaches me until I can do it with her on a monthly basis every time.
That's all for now.
I'm sure something good will happen!
This is the next episode of Apkami, featuring Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory and Morning Musume。 24's Abomigake and Ako.
Here is the next one!
JuiceJuice Tokyo Blur Vocal Recording
Vocal Recording of Tokyo Blur Dambar Rule from JuiceJuice's latest singleTokyo Blur from JuiceJuice's latest single
Also see the vocal recording of Dambarlulu
Yes, yes, yes.
What's not clear?
It's okay.
Okay.
Okay, let's do this.
Okay, first of all, I love you.
I'm gonna overflow tonight.
Let's do it up to...
Let's do it up to Afreso. Yes, let's do it up to Afreso. I love you, Tokyo, I'm going to overflow tonight.
Oh the whole feeling is great.
It's going to overflow tonight. Just a little more rhythm here.
It's going to overflow tonight. Let's get it out there.
Yes.
Is it okay if I say it backwards?
Do most of the girls say it with their own voices?
I should tell them I can do it with my own voice.
Yes, I'll try it. I'll try it! Tokyo is going to be overflowing tonight.
I'm depressed from Radio Caravelle.
Let's go to
I don't love you.
tokyo tonight
Radio Cara Rubble.
Rain forecast for tomorrow.
It's work, isn't it? Why are you feeling so good?
Rain forecast for tomorrow
Rain forecast.
Forecast there, don't shed your balls, yoo-hoo-hoo, and be firm.
Yes, OK.
It's work, isn't it?
Okay, okay, let's go to rust.
Okay, let's go to rust.
So, you can say "tsuratto" or you can split it down the middle.
Let's say "tsuratsu".
Here we go.
The story of birth, when you get out, at the corner of that moon
Dempitation, anticipation, love's end eye, come on, change it up
Dobile Hand Sleepless Love
Get out of the passenger seat, new me
Let's go see a new morning Graduation Night breeze gently brushing back my hair
Okay, okay, all the basics are done.
I just need to make the rhythm stand up a little more.
I'd like to make the rhythm stand up more firmly.
That's the image I'm going for.
So, new tomorrow, new me...
After that, let's go see the new morning.
Can you do "new morning" with your own voice?
I'll try it, yeah, yeah, me.
me, the clarification is gently graying in the wind.
I feel like my back voice is a little too strong, but I don't think I can handle a new morning with my natural voice.
I can't help but feel like I'm going to get some kind of beauty out of you.
Which is easier?
Is it best to use a softer, natural voice?
Yeah, I think so.
Can I try it from here? No, no, no, can I try?
Okay, let's try it one more time, and then we'll go see a new morning, a night breeze with the hair gently slicked back on the back of the head.
Okay, okay.
Then we'll do a little bit of hamo.
I'll have Mr. Damper tell you about it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Rust
Yes, sir.
You've got a lot of guts, don't you?
Yes, Hand Sleepless in Love's Rust, you've got a pretty big hamo, don't you?
Hand, get off the tree line of sleepless love
Let's do it once.
Let's do it once, OK new morning, let's go see
Yes, yes, yes
A new me, a new morning, let's go see.
Let's go take a look
A new morning, let's go see
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go see
Yes, let's go see
Covering the resin of love
Let's go see a new morning
Graduation
The night wind gently caressing the back of my hair
Let's go, let's go, let's go, gradation
Let's go, let's go
gradation
With me
A new morning
Let's go see
Graduation
I'll gently stroke the back of your hair
I stroke the wind
That's all.
Thank you very much.
OK, that's all. Yes, thank you very much.
Well, that was wonderful!
Well, well, I really, I don't know, your voice is really too nice, but I think I have it in me when I'm recording, I think I should sing like this, but I also do what you tell me to do, like softly.
Like softly.
I thought it was really wonderful that you were able to respond so quickly.
I also went to see JuiceJuice's performance at the Budokan the other day.
I heard this song then, too.
I wanted to listen to it again.
I really wanted to have this CD, so I was really happy to hear it now.
I was so happy to be able to listen to it now.
Your voice is so clear and clear.
It's like water or a very thick peach juice.
I really like your unique soft voice.
I'd like to listen to it a lot more in the future.
That's all for JuiceJuice Tokyo Bradambarulu's vocal recording.
JuiceJuice new single Tokyo Brown
Now on sale
You can do it
Ami Tanimoto and
Three-digit children have brought you Apkami
It's time to say goodbye!
We've seen a lot of videos this time.
I, Sangita, was very impressed with the recording of Mr. Danbara at the end.
I haven't done so many recordings myself yet, have I?
Mr. Danbara was moving so much during the recording
That left a great impression on me.
I've been so rigid that I'm not sure I'll be able to record like him next time.
So I thought I'd like to move a little like Mr. Danbara on the next recording.
And I, Tanimoto, was talking with Mao Akiyama and Mio Hirai at the Apkami photo studio.
I was talking about Mao Akiyama and Mio Hirai's Apkami Photo Gallery, and I thought they were two very cool dancers.
They are two very cool dancers, and they talked about the group and their various dances.
When they dance with gusto...
They really put themselves out there.
But when it comes to the cute ones...
But when it comes to the cute ones, they just go along with everyone else.
I was really happy to see that she was thinking about that.
I was really happy to see that.
At apkami, you can get a behind-the-scenes look at the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We'll be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time on Apkami, I'll be talking with Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory,
Morning Musume。24's Akiko Abomigeta.
Goodbye.
Next time on Apkami, we will have a dance lesson with JuiceJuice and Oaiko. And we will show you the recording of Angerumu Revital Ichigeki.
Enjoy. me.